var questions = [{
        question: 'Python created by',
        choices: [
            'Guido van Rossum',
            'Yukihiro Matsumoto',
            ' James Gosling',
            'Dennis Ritchie'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 0
    },
    {
        question: 'Ruby created by',
        choices: [
            'Larry Wall',
            ' Bjarne Stroustrup',
            'Rasmus Lerdorf',
            'Yukihiro Matsumoto'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 3
    },
    {
        question: 'Java created by',
        choices: [
            'Dennis Ritchie',
            'James Gosling',
            'John McCarthy',
            'Niklaus Wirth'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 1
    },
    {
        question: 'C created by',
        choices: [
            'Rasmus Lerdorf',
            'Dennis Ritchie',
            'Bjarne Stroustrup',
            'Guido van Rossum'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 1
    },
    {
        question: 'C++ created by',
        choices: [
            'Brendan Eich',
            'Niklaus Wirth',
            'Bjarne Stroustrup',
            'Dennis Ritchie'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 2
    },
    {
        question: 'PHP created by',
        choices: [
            'Guido van Rossum',
            'Yukihiro Matsumoto',
            'Bjarne Stroustrup',
            'Rasmus Lerdorf'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 3
    },
    {
        question: 'Perl created by',
        choices: ['Larry Wall', 'John McCarthy', 'Dennis Ritchie', 'Brendan Eich'],
        correctAnswer: 0
    },
    {
        question: 'JavaScript created by',
        choices: [
            'Niklaus Wirth',
            'Brendan Eich',
            'Rasmus Lerdorf',
            'Yukihiro Matsumoto'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 1
    },
    {
        question: 'Pascal created by',
        choices: [
            'John McCarthy',
            'Guido van Rossum',
            'James Gosling',
            'Niklaus Wirth'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 3
    },
    {
        question: 'Lisp created by',
        choices: [
            'Bjarne Stroustrup',
            'Rasmus Lerdorf',
            'John McCarthy',
            'Larry Wall'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 2
    }
];